NO BOY NO CRY ore zenshin GO
no boy, no cry, I advance go!
shounen yo kiite kure
hey boys, listen up
ningen nante taishita mon ja nai sa
humans aren't such a big deal
ashita nante moui ranai kara
who needs tomorrow anyway
nigitta kobushi wo kakusu na yo
so don't hide your fists
fuan ni yume wo
you're not old enough
uri tobasu hodo mada oiborechainai daro
to sell your dreams away to uncertainty
shounen yo kokoro no jyuu no
hey boys, you're the only ones
hikigane wo hikeru no wa kimi dake sa
who can pull the trigger in your heart
subete no wakamono wa iitta
all the kids said
doushi yo mo naku kudaranai
we're living in this senseless, ridiculous,
kono subarashii sekai ni tattaima ikiteiru kara
awesome world right at this moment,
subete no wakamono wa iitta
all the kids said
subete no hontou to uso wo
don't forget every truth or lie
kesshite wasurete shima wa nai you ni
subete no wakamono wa iitta
all the kids said
shinu ni wa mosugiru darou
we're way too young to die
shiraketa tsura ga naranderu karappo no kono machi de
in this empty town lined with empty faces
subete no wakamono wa iitta
all the kids took off
kaze no nai kono yoru ni
into this windless night
nanika wo kaeyou to shiteru kara
because they want to change something
Reach the Soul!
Fist of Love
Please don't die...
I'll get you out now.
Hey!
What are you doing there?
{CURRY OF LIFE SHOP
One, two...
Hope they're all right.
I'm sure they'll be able
to bring Karashi back.
Definitely, definitely.
One, two...
That's the Katabami Gold Mine...
Instead of just getting
Rokusuke and Karashi back
let's finish the Kurosuki Family
once and for all!
Don't get carried away, Naruto.
So what are we gonna do then?
I'm kind of worried about
what Guy-sensei told us.
The boss of the Kurosuki Family
may be
one of the Seven Ninja
Swordsmen of the Mist.
Who knows what
they'll do to Rokusuke?
Yeah, but how seriously
can we take Guy-sensei's info?
What are you talking about?!
Guy-sensei is always right!
Calm down, Lee.
We should investigate first.
Yeah!
Sir Raiga, we were able
to capture Rokusuke,
one of the three that
slipped out of the village.
Well done.
It seems that they went to ask
for some help from a Ninja village.
Where did you go?!
I'm sorry.
Don't bother rookie.
Yes sir!
Rokusuke, I thought we had
a good relationship
with everybody in the Gold Mine.
Well that's...
Why is it? I'm so deeply sorry
to hear that you left the village.
I can't remember how things
were in the past
when everything was going well.
I'm sorry, I'm sorry.
I won't do it again!
Yeah, I have a good idea.
I'm going to arrange
for your funeral.
Please don't! Please let me go!
I won't do it again
so please forgive me!
Why? Don't you like funerals?
No, I don't wanna die yet!
You know I really like funerals...
Think about it.
When they are alive humans speak ill
of each other,
they betray each other,
and they hate each other.
But at a funeral,
they forget all the hatred
they had for the other.
They even remember
the good times they had together.
Right?
You have to be kidding me!
No! Please don't do it.
Hey!
Let me go!
It's a done deal then.
Let's have a big funeral for Rokusuke.
— Yeah!
Come on!
Hurry up!
Is that gold?
There's nothing shiny about it.
They have to melt
that ore into mercury.
After that they evaporate it
and only then does it turn into pure gold.
I don't get it.
Well there is no need
for you to understand it.
Oh!
Huh? What are you doing?!
Hurry up!
If you don't hurry up
I'm gonna ask the boss
to let me hold your funeral!
Please forgive me!
I'm getting really mad now.
I won't forgive them!
Calm down, Naruto...
We don't know anything
about them yet.
That's right. We should do
what Neji is telling us.
Yeah but...
if we don't do something
that poor old guy is going to die!
Naruto, leave things to me here.
Wait, Lee!
Hey, hey.
Hurry up and pick them up!
Yeah! Way to go Lee!
Are you okay old man?
Oh my gosh!
What have you done?!
Here. Drink some water.
What are you doing?!
I beg you.
Please punch me, kick me.
Please knock me around
like the way you just did
with those guys.
What are you saying?
If you won't do it
I'll do it myself!
What are you doing?!
Stop!
I'm scared.
Just think what they'll do
if they knew I was
the only one that was safe.
What was that sound?
Did they find us?
Oh my, that's the sound
of the funeral bell.
Funeral?
Yeah.
Raiga, the boss of the Kurosuki family
which rules this town
arranges a funeral for
those who betray him.
He buries them alive.
What? They bury them alive?
That's so cruel!
Yeah but...
Raiga always cries sadly
during the funeral.
That's one weird guy.
But...
That doesn't seem to be
the sound of the bell for you.
Yeah, I heard that Rokusuke
was caught this morning so...
What?!
I'm so happy I remember
the first day I met that guy.
Yeah? That's nice.
Yeah... When I told him we were taking
over the mountain from the magistrate
he was so relieved to be freed from
the high taxes that he was paying.
He was laughing out of pure joy...
He was a really nice guy.
I like funerals.
Makes me feel nostalgic.
Would you put on
a big funeral for me too?
Fool! I'm not putting on
a funeral for you.
You are not going
to die before me.
I don't have to have a funeral for you
to think of the good times
because you are always a good boy.
Raiga.
What is it?
They're coming.
They'll show up anytime now.
Yeah... I'm excited to see
what kind of help he sought.
Okay! Let's save the guy.
Let's do it, Neji.
Okay.
Byakugan!
It's all right. He's still alive.
If we can get rid of
the guys around him
we can save him.
Okay! Let's get rid
of them quickly!
Yeah!
Okay, let's go!
No...! Let me out!
An enemy attack!
You...!
Tenten, you take the right!
Okay!
Gentle Fist!
Shadow Clone Jutsu!
U-Zu-Ma-Ki...
Naruto Barrage!
That's the way!
— Watch out!
— Huh?
There are three more!
Here comes the Leaf Village's
Handsome Devil Rock Lee!
I found the last one!
You are...
Who is this guy?
Well...
This is Karashi.
The one Grandma Sansho
was talking about...
This is Karashi?
Karashi, was it your own decision
to join the Kurosuki Family...
just like Grandma Sansho said it was?
So what if it was?
What?!
Sir Raiga is great!
He dethroned the old evil government
of the Katabami Gold Mine
and he liberated everybody
from the village!
One, two, one, two...
Umm, Grandma...
Oh my...
You are so greedy!
They are fighting their lives
out there by going into the gold mine...
Can't you just wait at least
while I'm cooking the curry?
I don't mind waiting but...
I think something is burning.
What?
Oh my, oh my...
Oops...
Yeah, it burned...
Karashi, did you know that
Grandma Sansho worries about you
everyday while cooking curry?
Naruto, leave things to me here.
Karashi, you saved my life
with your curry of life.
If you can make such
a wonderful curry,
how can you stay with the family of
a man with no respect for life?!
Why?
Nobody cares to compliment me
even if I can make that curry.
As a man born in this world
I should gain more power and
try to take over the world!
Instead of sitting around in that store
that no one patronizes anymore.
What? I can't take this anymore!
Lee!
Karashi, not only did you and
Grandma Sansho's curry save my life...
But you also taught me that
if you make it from the heart
just one serving of curry
could save lives
and that even somebody like me
could do anything just by trying hard.
You looked much stronger
and dignified then than you do now.
Karashi!
I've never seen anybody
who tries this hard.
I see. You want to save
this boy too, huh...
Please promise me...
Please get out of the Kurosuki Family!
You're right...
I'm sorry... I'm so sorry!
Oh, I'm so relieved.
Hey! Please get me out of here.
It's dark and I can't breathe.
Oh yeah!
We almost forgot
about Rokusuke.
Mmm? You guys...
Sorry to keep you waiting.
It's all right now.
I'm sorry. Thinking that maybe
I could still save my friend
who got buried alive...
I just couldn't stay still.
Yeah, I understand.
Neji, what is it?
What is this?
This feeling of danger...
Hey Neji, what is it?
We are being watched.
It's probably Raiga.
What?
From the top of that cliff...
Okay. Let's go!
Karashi, please take care of Rokusuke.
All right.
No one's here.
Where did he go?
Mmm? What is that?
This mist...
Ninja Art: Hidden Mist Jutsu!
Hidden Mist Jutsu...
A specialty of Mist Village Ninja.
So what Guy-sensei said was true?
Damn, I can't see anything!
Neji, try to find the enemy
with your Byakugan.
I've been trying...!
Uh... Can't see a thing!
That's impossible.
Even Neji's Byakugan
that's supposed to let him
see 360 degrees won't work!
What's going on?
There isn't supposed to be
a Jutsu that can break Byakugan!
What do you think, Ranmaru?
It's amazing...
One of them can see through
the Chakra Network.
He probably has some sort
of Kekkei Genkai power.
He can see us?
It's all right
my power is superior to his...
So what are you going to do?
Everybody in the Katabami
Gold Mine is depending on me.
I'm the one who has to
keep the peace of this village.
Are you going to hold a funeral?
No even if I hold a funeral
I have no memories of them.
I'll just get rid of them!
Look
Ninja Art: Lightning Fang!
Wh-What is it?!
Lightning! Drop!
What do you think, Ranmaru?
It's great, Raiga!
kusottare na nyuusu ga toori sugite
crappy news pass us by
kimi wa kotoba wo nakusu
and you become speechless
boku no koe ja marude chiisa sugite
my voice is way too soft
kimi wa henji mo shinai
so you don't answer
kimi ga naiteru hitori de naiteru
you're crying, crying alone
boku wa dou suru boku mo naiteru no sa
what can I do? I'm crying too
yoru ni hitoribocchi no ore no sakebi ni nosete
"let my lonely scream ring out through the night"
zawameku jidai wo ore no supiido de buttobashiteku yeah yeah yeah yeah
I'll thrash this confused era with my speed, yeah
sanzameku yoru mo ore no supiido de buttobashiteku yeah yeah yeah yeah
and I'll thrash this confused night with my speed, yeah
tsunzaku gitaa to ore no supiido de buttobashiteku yeah yeah yeah yeah
I'll thrash them with my piercing guitar and my speed, yeah
katamuku sekai mo warui yatsura mo kechirashiteku yeah yeah yeah yeah
I'll take this sinking world, all its evil bastards, and kick their butts, yeah
Naruto Barrage! What?
Leaf Hurricane! Mm?
Here I come! Huh?
Impossible!
Hey! The enemy disappeared!
I have nobody either!
What? There is no enemy!
Neji! Are you using
your Byakugan correctly?!
I am doing it right!
It's impossible but my Byakugan
is picking up Chakra!
Next time:
"Byakugan's Natural Enemy."